var data = [
  {
    content: "Mountain climbing was interesting! But you slept in the Amazons and now feel the following: ",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "liver flukes",
      "kidney failure",
      "cough and catarghh"
    ],
    options: [
      "running nose",
      "flu",
      "Malaria"
    ],
    answer: "Common cold",
  },
  {
    content: "You were cut by an infected razor blade and now you don\'t feel very well",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "chronic fatigue",
      "rapid weight loss",
      "night sweats"
    ],
    options: [
      "HIV/AIDS",
      "Cancer",
      "Tuberculosis"
    ],
    answer: "HIV/AIDS",
    answer_summary: "Human immunodeficiency virus infection and acquired immune deficiency syndrome (HIV/AIDS) is a spectrum of conditions caused by infection with the human immunodeficiency virus (HIV). Following initial infection, a person may not notice any symptoms or may experience a brief period of influenza-like illness. Typically, this is followed by a prolonged period with no symptoms. As the infection progresses, it interferes more with the immune system, increasing the risk of common infections like tuberculosis, as well as other opportunistic infections, and tumors that rarely affect people who have working immune systems. These late symptoms of infection are referred to as AIDS. This stage is often also associated with weight loss."
  },
  {
    content: "You just ate a contaminated fruit in the garden",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "bloody stools",
      "fever",
      "vomiting"
    ],
    options: [
      "Peptic Ulcer",
      "Diarrhea",
      "Typhoid"
    ],
    answer: "Diarrhea"
  },
  {
    content: "You just collapsed to the ground due to so much pain around your body",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "inflammatory chest pain",
      "joint stiffness",
      "fatigue"
    ],
    options: [
      "Peptic Ulcer",
      "Diarrhoea",
      "Arthritis"
    ],
    answer: "Arthritis",
    answer_summary: "Arthritis is a form of joint disorder that involves inflammation in one or more joints. There are over 100 different forms of arthritis. The most common form of arthritis is osteoarthritis (degenerative joint disease), a result of trauma to the joint, infection of the joint, or age."
  },
  {
    content: "You just all of a sudden started having severe muscle pains",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "abnormal reflexes",
      "headache",
      "breathing problems",
      "sudden paralysis"
    ],
    options: [
      "Poliomyelitis",
      "Brain Tumor",
      "Stroke"
    ],
    answer: "Poliomyelitis"
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "fever",
      "headache",
      "chills",
      "fatigue"
    ],
    options: [
      "Malaria",
      "Yellow fever",
      "Diabetes"
    ],
    answer: "Yellow fever",
    answer_summary: "Yellow fever, known historically as yellow jack, yellow plague, or bronze john, is an acute viral disease. In most cases, symptoms include fever, chills, loss of appetite, nausea, muscle pains particularly in the back, and headaches. Symptoms typically improve within five days. In some people within a day of improving, the fever comes back, abdominal pain occurs, and liver damage begins causing yellow skin. If this occurs, the risk of bleeding and kidney problems is also increased."
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "fever",
      "weigth loss",
      "abdominal pain",
      "nosebleeds"
    ],
    options: [
      "Warts",
      "Vasculitis",
      "Wilson's Disease"
    ],
    answer: "Vasculitis",
    answer_summary: "Vasculitis (plural: vasculitides) is a group of disorders that destroy blood vessels by inflammation. Both arteries and veins are affected. Lymphangitis is sometimes considered a type of vasculitis.Vasculitis is primarily caused by leukocyte migration and resultant damage."
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "fatigue",
      "pneumonia",
      "high fever",
      "nosebleeds"
    ],
    options: [
      "Typhoid fever",
      "Malaria",
      "Influenza"
    ],
    answer: "Typhoid fever"
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "chest pain",
      "fever",
      "weakness",
      "weight loss",
      "dry cough"
    ],
    options: [
      "Typhoid fever",
      "Influenza",
      "Tuberculosis"
    ],
    answer: "Tuberculosis"
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "fever",
      "lethargy",
      "appetite loss"
    ],
    options: [
      "Tularemia",
      "Malaria",
      "Yellow fever"
    ],
    answer: "Tularemia",
    answer_summary: "Tularemia (or tularaemia; also known as Pahvant Valley plague, rabbit fever, deer fly fever, and Ohara's fever) is a serious infectious disease caused by the intracellular bacterium Francisella tularensis."
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "abdominal pain",
      "diarrhea",
      "weight loss"
    ],
    options: [
      "Flu",
      "Trichuriasis",
      "Trypanosomiasis"
    ],
    answer: "Trichuriasis",
    answer_summary: "Trichuriasis, also known as whipworm infection, is an infection by the parasitic worm Trichuris trichiura (whipworm). If infection is only with a few worms, there are often no symptoms. In those who are infected with many worms, there may be abdominal pain, tiredness and diarrhea. The diarrhea sometimes contains blood. Infections in children may cause poor intellectual and physical development. Low red blood cell levels may occur due to loss of blood."
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "nausea",
      "diarrhea",
      "heartburn",
      "muscle pain",
      "fatigue"
    ],
    options: [
      "Malaria",
      "Trichinosis",
      "Dysentry"
    ],
    answer: "Trichinosis"
  },
  {
    content: "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "drooling",
      "spasms",
      "irregular heartbeat",
      "excessive sweating",
      "fever"
    ],
    options: [
      "Tetanus",
      "Trichinosis",
      "Yellow fever"
    ],
    answer: "Tetanus"
  },
  {
    content: "It has to be a bug! You got bitten by something and noticed the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "fever",
      "chills",
      "headaches",
      "muscle aches",
      "nausea"
    ],
    options: [
      "Common cold",
      "Influenza (flu)",
      "Relapsing fever"
    ],
    answer: "Relapsing fever",
    answer_summary: "Relapsing fever is a vector-borne disease caused by infection with certain bacteria in the genus Borrelia, which are transmitted through the bites of lice or soft-bodied ticks."
  },
  {
    content: "You went hiking! A bug could've gotten a better part of your arm. You notice you have the following persistent symptoms",
    question: "What are you likely to come down with?",
    symptoms: [
      "appetite loss",
      "perspiration",
      "headaches",
      "muscle pain",
      "nausea",
      "diarrhea",
      "vomiting"
    ],
    options: [
      "Q fever",
      "Influenza (flu)",
      "Common cold"
    ],
    answer: "Q fever",
    answer_summary: "Q fever is a disease caused by infection with Coxiella burnetii, a bacterium that affects humans and other animals. This organism is uncommon, but may be found in cattle, sheep, goats, and other domestic mammals, including cats and dogs. The infection results from inhalation of a spore-like small-cell variant, and from contact with the milk, urine, feces, vaginal mucus, or semen of infected animals."
  },
  {
    "content": "You were bitten by a bug! You notice you have the following  number of persistent symptoms",
    "question": "What are you likely to come down with?",
    "symptoms": [
      "Bleeding into joints or muscles",
      "Bruising easily",
      "Nosebleeds that do not stop easily",
      "Excessive bleeding with surgical procedures"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Bleeding Disorder",
      "bleeding into the brain",
      "bleeding into the joints",
    ],
    "answer": "Bleeding Disorder",
    "answer_summary": "Coagulopathy (also called a bleeding disorder) is a condition in which the bloodâ€™s ability to coagulate (form clots) is impaired. This condition can cause a tendency toward prolonged or excessive bleeding (bleeding diathesis or bleeding disorder), which may occur spontaneously or following an injury or medical and dental procedures."
  },
  {
    "content": "You feel a sharp pain in your belly minutes after a meal, giving you feelings of ",
    "question": "This could indicate signs of",
    "symptoms": [
      "Nausea",
      "Abdominal pain and cramps",
      "Fever"
    ],
    "options": [
      "vomiting",
      "weakness",
      "Food Poisoning"
    ],
    "answer": "Food Poisoning",
    "answer_summary": "Foodborne illness (also foodborne disease and colloquially referred to as food poisoning) is any illness resulting from the food spoilage of contaminated food, pathogenic bacteria, viruses, or parasites that contaminate food, as well as chemical or natural toxins such as poisonous mushrooms and various species of beans that have not been boiled for at least 10 minutes."
  },
  {
    "content": "After standing for a long time, you start feeling some symptoms of ",
    "question": "",
    "symptoms": [
      "lightheadedness",
      "depression",
      "loss of consciousness"
    ],
    "options": [
      "Hypertension",
      "Low Blood Pressure",
      "Elevated Blood Pressure"
    ],
    "answer": "Hypertension"
  }
]
